it's true, but let's-let's
consider for a moment
(Stuart:)that possibly I'm the problem.
Yeah.
(Stuart:)You are.
You can say it.
Okay, fine. What...?
(Stuart:)I mean, what
can I do?
(Stuart:)I get so nervous
around women.
(Penny:)Well, you're talking
to us now.
(Penny:)I mean, you don't seem nervous.
(Sheldon:)Well, that's
'cause I'm doing that trick
(Stuart:)where you imagine
the audience is naked.
(Stuart:)By the way, thumbs up, ladies.
(Amy:)Do you not hear
how creepy that sounds?
(laughing):
It was a joke.
(Bernadette:)Was it?
(Stuart:)No, I'm still doing it.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Penny:)Don't be offended, but...
(Penny:)what went wrong with you?
I-I guess I assumed
at this point in my life,
(Stuart:)I would be married
or in a relationship,
(Stuart:)or even have a pet
(Stuart:)that didn't run away
or kill itself.
(Bernadette:)That really happened?
(Stuart:)I mean, I can't say for sure,
but I swear
(Stuart:)that rabbit looked me
right in the eye
(Stuart:)before it hopped
in front of that car.
(Stuart:)Anyway,